{
    "id": "1cca17d43e374c3cbae5bf49688c2ae9",
    "title": "Much, Many, A Lot, A Lot Of",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2b55501557d54927a9ec40c6fa5f925b",
            "title": "Much, Many, A Lot, A Lot Of",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How ............................ brothers and sisters do you have?",
                    "description": "Use many with plural nouns in questions and negatives.",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She doesn't have .............................. money.",
                    "description": "Either much or a lot of is possible here.",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "many",
                        "a lot of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He did ............................. for me when he was alive.",
                    "description": "Much is not normally used in affirmative sentences.",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "a lot",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She doesn't read ................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much",
                        "a lot of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has ................................. friends.",
                    "description": "Many is not normally used in affirmative sentences. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "a lot of",
                        "much",
                        "many",
                        "a lot"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There aren't .............................. apples on the tree.",
                    "description": "Either many or a lot of is possible here.  A lot of can be used in affirmative, negative and interrogative sentences. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much",
                        "a lot of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have been watching ............................... movies recently.",
                    "description": "Many is not normally used in affirmative sentences. Either lots of or a lot of can be used here.",
                    "answers": [
                        "a lot of",
                        "lots of",
                        "many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ate ................................ food.",
                    "description": "A lot cannot be used before a noun. Use a lot of.",
                    "answers": [
                        "a lot",
                        "a lot of",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "....................................... social problems are caused by poverty.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "A lot of",
                        "Much",
                        "A lot"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her condition hasn't improved ................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "many",
                        "a lot"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I didn't know ................................ people at the party.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much",
                        "a lot of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have been partying ............................... these days.",
                    "description": "A lot of is used before a noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "a lot",
                        "a lot of",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}